A DynamoDB Stream is an ongoing flow of events,
A发电机 DB 流是一个持续的事件流
which includes all changes made to a Dynamo table.
包括对 Dynamo 表进行的所有更改
This event stream will be empty if there are no changes being made to a table.
如果未对表进行任何更改 那么此事件流将为空
But when table changes are made,
但当表改变时
an event will be placed into the DynamoDB Stream for each change.
事件将被放入 DynamoDB 流中的每个更改
This includes all change events: creating,
这包括所有更改事件: 创建
updating, deleting any item in the table.
更新 删除表中的任何项
Operations that only read items from table will not be included in the stream.
仅从表中读取项的操作将不包含在流中
So why do we want this?
我们为什么要这样呢 ?
Streams allow you to take an action on a change to the database.
流允许您对数据库进行更改
For example, if you wanted to track how many new accounts were created over time,
例如 如果您想要跟踪随时间推移创建的新帐户数
you could have an application process your stream and take an action on
您可以让应用程序处理流并对其执行操作
each create event or if you wanted to send
每个创建事件或者如果要发送
an INET message to a user for setting a high score in an online game,
对用户的 INET 消息 用于在在线游戏中设置高分数
you could use a lambda function to compare
你可以用 lambda 函数来比较
any score increases to the current leader board.
任何分数都将增加到当前领导板
There are many potential uses for DynamoDB Streams,
DynamoDB Streams 有许多潜在用途
including DynamoDB global tables,
包括 DynamoDB 全局表
otherwise known as multi-region redundancy.
否则称为多区域冗余
DynamoDB Streams are used to create global tables.
" 发电机 " 流用于创建全局表
A global table is a DynamoDB table replicated across regions.
全局表是跨区域复制的 DynamoDB 表
As you've seen, creating multi-region services is usually not trivial.
正如您所看到的 创建多区域服务通常不是小事
However, this is one case where it's actually quite simple.
但是 这是一个非常简单的案例
You enable DynamoDB Streams and then
启用 DynamoDB Streams  然后
select the region to which you would like to replicate your table.
选择要复制表的区域
AWS takes care of the rest.
AWS 负责休息
Global tables are active, active.
全局表是活动的 活动的
This means that you can write to the table in
这意味着您可以在以下目录中写入表 :
any region and the changes propagate to all of the other regions.
任何区域和更改都传播到所有其他区域
This is different from the read replica model that many RDS services follow,
这与许多 RDS 服务遵循的读取副本模型不同
where the replicated data can only be read.
复制的数据只能读取的位置
Being active, active allows you to run services in multiple region and
活动时 活动允许您在多个区域中运行服务
have those applications access the data locally and operate with some autonomy,
这些应用程序在本地访问数据并运行一些自治
which creates even more redundancy in your environment.
从而在您的环境中创建更多冗余
DynamoDB takes advantage of
发电机利用
the AWS network backbone to provide low latency data replication across regions.
AWS 网络主干 用于跨区域提供低延迟数据复制
Multi-region active, active datastores are a big deal.
多区域活动的活动数据存储器是一个很大的交易
Many databases and services are unable to accomplish this,
许多数据库和服务无法完成此任务
or they require a large amount of effort to set up and maintain.
或者需要大量的努力来设置和维护
For use cases that require it,
对于需要它的用例
DynamoDB offers tremendous resiliency.
" 发电机 " 提供了巨大的弹性